[ childish laughing ]
[ children singing spookily ]
Subtitles by explosiveskull Sync by GoldenBeard
[ Georgie ] You 'll float , too !
You 'll float , too !
[ Young Beverly ] I saw all of us .
All of us were there .
Back in the cistern .
But we were older .
We were our parents ' ages .
Am I still handsome as an adult ?
[ boys chuckling ]
You grow into your looks .
- [ Young Eddie laughs ] - What the fuck does that mean ?
What about me ?
Like now ,
but taller .
Swear it .
Swear if It isn 't dead ,
if It ever comes back ,
we 'll come back , too .
[ Mike ] Memory ,
it 's a funny thing .
People want to believe they are
what they choose to remember .
The good stuff .
The moments .
The places .
The people we all hold on to .
[ wind blowing ]
But sometimes ...
sometimes
we are what we wish we could forget .
[ children screaming ]
[ screaming ]
- [ carnival music playing ] - [ lively chattering ]
[ carny ] Okay , kids .
Get ready .
- Go ! - [ bell dings ]
Who 's it gonna be ?
First one to pop their balloon 's a winner !
It could be anyone ! We got a real
- barn burner here , folks . - Come on . Come on . Come on .
[ carny ] It 's getting close .
Who 's gonna catch the leader , huh ?
Who 's gonna be the big winner tonight ?
- Oh , yeah ! - Whoo !
[ bell dinging ]
Winner , winner , chicken dinner .
- Thank you . - Wow .
You really showed ' em , huh ?
I did . I ...
Yeah .
Hey , girl , do you want this ? [ clicking tongue ]
[ whispering ] Thanks for letting me win .
Yeah .
[ Victoria 's mom ] What 'd you get , Vicky ?
[ Don ] Aww . Such a gentleman .
[ Victoria 's mom ] Look at that !
Well , here is your consolation prize .
Look at that .
Never been a fan of the beaver ,
but look at this hat . I mean ...
Thank you .
So , we need to talk logistics .
Ooh . How romantic .
Romantic ?
What 's so fucking romantic , huh ?
- [ spits ] - [ Webby ] Hey .
Your mommas ever teach you boys to respond to someone
when they ask you a fucking question ?
Come on , Adrian .
You got a problem , faggot ?
I don 't , but Meg Ryan called .
She wants her wig back .
[ Don ] All right . All right .
Come on . Come on , Adrian .
Stuff like that is
why I have to leave this shithole town .
Small minds .
They have small dicks .
I 'm being serious .
We belong elsewhere .
Hey , look , if you end up hating New York ,
we can always move back here .
[ Adrian ] I just want to be with you .
I don 't care . New York , Derry , whatever . It 's ...
You have to say that .
I don 't have to say anything .
Take off that fucking hat .
- Oh , God . - Come on , let 's go .
[ Webby ] Wouldn 't want to give people the impression
we allow a bunch of fucking fairies like you in this town .
Yeah , he was born here , asshole .
- All right , let 's go . - No . You know what ?
I 'll take off the hat for you .
But why leave it there ?
Anything else you would like me
to take off for you tonight ?
Any special requests , ladies ?
[ all grunting ]
[ Webby ] Fucker !
- [ Don ] Let him go ! - [ Don and Adrian groan ]
- [ coughing ] - [ wheezing ]
- What 's that ? - Stop .
I don 't think you 'll be needing that .
- [ Don ] Leave him alone ! - [ Chris ] Hit him .
He 's got asthma , fucker ! [ groans ]
[ groans ]
- [ groaning ] - [ Chris laughing ]
- [ wheezing ] - Come on !
- [ groans ] - Fuck him up !
[ Webby ] Come on , kick him !
Come on , kick the shit out of him .
Adrian ! [ grunting ]
- [ coughing ] - [ Chris laughing ]
I still hate your fucking hair .
Adrian !
- Get the fuck off him ! - [ continues coughing ]
Look what you did to his fucking face !
Hey ! Hey ! Help me get him up .
[ Don ] Adrian . [ groans ]
Help me get this fucking punk up right now .
[ groaning ]
Give me the hat , Chris .
It 's fucking mine !
I said give me the fucking hat !
[ Don ] Adrian !
[ Adrian wheezing ]
You like that ?
Welcome to Derry , motherfucker .
[ Don ] No ! Adrian !
No !
[ train horn blowing ]
Let 's get the fuck out of here .
- Let 's go ! - [ Don ] No !
Adrian !
Help !
Help me !
Somebody !
[ continues wheezing ]
Somebody fucking help me !
[ panting ]
- Oh ... - [ Adrian gasping ]
Adrian .
[ Adrian wheezing ]
- [ Adrian screaming ] - No !
[ Adrian groaning ]
[ faint distorted carnival music playing ]
Adrian !
[ whimpering ]
[ children ] We all float down here !
[ Mike ] Thing is ,
sometimes what we wish was forgotten ,
what we tried to leave in the past ,
won 't stay there .
- [ radio beeping ] - [ gasps ]
[ dispatcher ] Units , please respond .
I 'm getting reports of a body found dismembered .
[ officer ] Come back . Was that " dismembered " ?
[ dispatcher ] That 's affirmative .
Scene is near the south entrance
of the festival grounds .
[ officer ] Copy that . En route .
Any directive for TC ?
[ dispatcher ] That 's affirmative .
Chief said to tape off the Derry Street Bridge .
[ Mike ] Sometimes , it comes back for you .
[ chattering on radio continues indistinctly ]
[ indistinct chatter ]
[ knocking on door ]
- [ door opens ] - Ah .
[ keys clicking ]
Mr. Denbrough ? They need you on set .
We 're just going to go this way .
- I 'm doing it . I 'm doing it . - No , don 't !
[ man ] Hey ! Clear the door !
Oh , come on . You 've never seen Indiana Jones ?
Watch your back .
Hey , hey . You a crewmember ?
I 'm the writer .
[ construction noises ]
[ assistant whispers ] Your husband 's here .
Hey ! Do you have the pages ?
[ woman ] Everyone , keep clear of the crane .
My friend , a film needs an ending .
- You do know that , right ? - Oh , yeah .
You said that you needed another day
to finish the pages ,
and we 're shooting this thing . It 's tonight .
That 's , like , 17 hours ...
Everybody , calm down , okay ?
I 'm calm .
I want you to be happy with the movie .
You understand ? I 'm on your side .
That 's great . ' Cause in my book , the ending ...
Is terrible .
All due respect , people loved your book . Loved .
They hated the ending .
You said you liked the ending .
That was a lie .
- We gotta do better , okay ? - Yeah .
Audra , you have my notes . Would you ...
Okay , thank you very much . Take me back to one , please .
Bye .
You have his notes ?
He 's not wrong .
You hate my endings , too ?
Not all your endings .
But this ...
- Okay . - Just ...
What ? Do you want me to keep lying to you
- just because I 'm your wife ? - You 're my wife ?
No . No . But you know what ?
You 've been blowing smoke up my ass for eight years ?
I guess I thought you were someone else .
I have not been blowing smoke up your ass .
Everybody wants a happy ending .
Everybody wants closure .
But that 's not the way life works out .
I think what Peter wants and what the studio wants ...
The studio ? When 'd you become a company man ?
Jesus , you 're an artist .
Come on . What 's wrong with just doing it
the way it 's written ? The way I wanted .
What 's wrong with being the woman I want you to be ?
Fuck you , Bill .
[ stammering ] On the page . The part , I mean . Not you .
- [ cell phone ringing ] - [ sighs ]
Hello ?
Bill Denbrough ? It 's Mike .
Mike who ?
Mike Hanlon .
- From Derry . - [ groaning ]
You need to come home .
[ breathing heavily ]
[ car horns honking ]
[ Myra on phone ] Eddie , I keep telling you
not to scare me like this .
And you never listen to me .
All right . Myra , please . Not now .
You shouldn 't be out there .
Eddie , it 's not safe to drive
when the roads are slick like this .
Sweetheart , it stopped raining , like ,
three hours ago . All right ?
- Everything is gonna be fine . - [ horn honking ]
Hey , dickhead ! Flow of traffic mean anything to you ?
What if you hydroplane ?
I 'm not gonna hydroplane .
It is my job to assess risk .
So , please trust me when I tell you
that , statistically speaking ,
I am much more likely to get into an accident
because I am talking to you on the phone !
All right ? I have to go .
I will talk to you soon . Goodbye .
[ phone ringing ]
Edward Kaspbrak speaking .
You didn 't say , " Okay , bye , I love you , "
like you usually do .
Listen to me . I can 't !
I 'm going to be late to this ...
meeting .
Say " I love you , " Eddie .
Okay , I love you , Mommy .
What ?
- Myra . Bye . - [ beeps ]
Hello ? Who 's this ?
It 's me . Mike .
Mike who ?
[ taxi horn blaring ]
[ Mike ] Eddie ! You okay ?
[ Eddie ] Yeah , I 'm pretty good .
Dude ! Dude , what the fuck ?
You were fine , like , five seconds ago .
- Who was it ? Who called ? Huh ? - [ breathing heavily ]
Rich ? Rich ? Talk to me .
You 're on in two minutes . You good ?
' Cause you look not good .
- I 'm fine . - You 're fine ? Okay .
And we 're walking . We 're walking .
Sixty seconds .
Even faster . All right .
Can we get him a bottle of water , maybe ?
- Bourbon . - Bourbon . Sure , sure .
And a mint .
It is showtime .
- I don 't think I can do this . - It 's what you do .
- You kill . You 're a killer . - That was fast .
Okay . We are good to go , and ...
Hey ! Where we going ? Where we going ?
- No . This way . Attaboy . - [ bell ringing ]
Okay .
All right . How do I look ?
Your hands are shaking , Rich .
Shit .
[ announcer ] Ladies and gentlemen ,
please welcome Richie Tozier !
- [ audience cheering ] - [ music playing ]
All right . How are we doing tonight ?
So , my girlfriend caught me masturbating
to her friend 's Facebook page .
[ audience laughing ]
And so now I 'm in Masturbators Anonymous .
And I stand up at the first meeting
and I say , " My name is Richie Trashmouth . "
- [ boy 1 ] Trashmouth . - [ boy 2 ] Shut up , Richie .
- [ boy 3 ] Fucking perv . - [ boy 4 ] Shut up , Richie .
[ boy 5 echoing ] Pussy !
Trashmouth . Uh ...
Forgot the joke .
[ scattered applause ]
[ woman ] You suck !
[ chuckles awkwardly ]
[ man ] Thank you , ladies and gentlemen ,
for letting us present to you today .
Now , this will include over a million square feet
of commercial and residential space .
State-of-the-art office towers .
What I 'm really looking for is to understand
how we create even more retail opportunities .
If we put in walls here and all along here ...
[ Ben on speaker ] Lose them .
With all due respect , Mr. Hanscom ...
Ben , please . And with all due respect to you ,
I 'm getting claustrophobic
just looking at this model . Aren 't you ?
Look . Throw up more walls , it 's gonna feel like a prison .
You know what people want to do in prison ?
Get out . Right ?
This should be a place that brings people together .
A meeting ground .
A clubhouse .
And if ,
- while people are there ... - [ cell phone ringing ]
Excuse me for one second .
- Hello ? - [ Mike ] Ben ?
It 's Mike Hanlon . From Derry .
[ operatic music playing ]
[ Patty ] Should I just book it ?
You 're sure you can get away from work ?
It 's summer , why not ?
Okay , we are Buenos Aires-bound .
[ Patty chuckles happily ]
[ cell phone ringing ]
Stanley Uris speaking .
It 's Mike .
I 'm sorry ?
Mike Hanlon .
From Derry .
Mike .
God , sorry . Yes , hi . [ chuckles nervously ]
[ stammering ] I don 't know why I didn 't ...
How long 's it been ? [ chuckles ]
A long time .
27 years .
It 's come back , hasn 't it ?
That 's why you 're calling me ?
It 's starting again , Stan .
Bad things are happening .
[ stammering ] Did you call the others ?
I mean , what if they don 't come ?
We made a promise , remember ?
How soon can you get here ?
Um ...
Well , I ... [ stammers ]
Yeah , I would need to do a few things ...
Tomorrow .
We don 't have much time .
I 'll text you everything you need .
I 'll see you soon , Stan the Man .
[ water running ]
[ breathing heavily ]
[ mouthing ] Do you swear ?
I swear , Bill .
[ Stanley gasps ]
[ gasps ]
- [ cell phone ringing ] - [ gasps ]
[ Mike ] You made a promise , Beverly .
[ Beverly ] I 'm so sorry , Mike .
I don 't even really remember .
Haven 't you ever wondered why you can 't seem
to remember the things most people should
about where they 're from , about who they are ,
why you have that scar on your hand ?
No one else remembered , either .
Eddie , Ben , Stan , Richie ...
Bill .
You have to come back .
You all do .
When ?
- [ gasps ] - Whoa .
Are you okay ? What 's going on ?
It 's the middle of the night . You 're packing ?
I didn 't want to wake you , honey .
I know this week 's been really exhausting .
I just got a phone call from an old friend from Derry .
I have to go back there .
It 's really hard to explain why .
It 's okay .
You don 't have to explain yourself to me . Relax .
I trust you .
Thank you .
I just don 't understand why you 'd lie to me .
I heard you .
You said the name Mike .
Yes , my friend .
See , there was a group of us back then ,
and we all made a promise to each other when we were kids .
You know trust is everything in a relationship .
You know it 's everything to me , right ?
- I know . This isn 't ... - Right ?
What ? Like the last time ?
I never cheated on you . [ whimpers ]
You 're a bad fucking liar ,
- Bev . - [ groaning ]
You 're not going anywhere , okay ?
I want you to stay right here ,
and you 're gonna show me
what it is you 're gonna do with Mike . Okay ?
You 're hurting me , honey .
No one else is gonna love you like me .
- You know that , right ? - [ grunts ]
[ Tom groans ]
[ stammering ] I 'm sorry .
- [ whimpering ] - [ grunting ]
Don 't make this fucking harder !
Don 't .
[ Beverly groaning ]
- [ grunts ] - [ groans ]
[ groaning ]
[ Tom yelling ]
[ groans ]
[ panting ]
You 're nothing without me ! You know that , right ?
Tell me I 'm wrong !
[ horn honks ]
[ children 's voices echoing ]
[ gasps ]
[ screaming ]
[ police radio chatter ]
[ Borton ] Jesus Christ .
Boys .
Little prick 's got balls , I 'll give him that .
Far enough , Bowers !
I 'm not done yet .
I 'm not done . I 'm not fucking done .
- On your knees . - I can 't . No !
I gotta kill them all ! Fuck , fuck !
Fucking kill them all ! Stop it !
- Cuff this sorry sack of shit ! - Fuck you ! [ yells ]
Fuck you !
Henry Bowers , I am placing you under arrest
for the murder of Oscar Bowers .
Do you understand , dipshit ?
You have the right to an attorney .
You have the right to remain silent .
[ laughing ]
[ nurse ] Bowers !
Bowers , calm the fuck down !
[ indistinct announcement on PA ]
[ Henry laughing ]
Someone needs a little extra clozapine today , don 't they ?
Stay in your fucking room .
- [ bed creaks ] - [ gasps ]
[ gasps ]
[ creature chuckling ]
[ screams ]
[ creature groaning ]
Hockstetter .
My knife .
[ music playing ]
- Whoa . - Careful .
This way .
Thanks a lot .
- [ Mike ] Hey . - Oh ...
- Mike , you look good . - Bill .
Yup . Whoa . Hey . How you doing ?
Bill .
I didn 't know if any of you would ...
I mean , after all this time ...
- Yeah . - But of course you came .
You know , an oath is an oath .
Losers
gotta stick together , right ?
The Losers .
You remember that . That 's good .
What else do you remember ?
I am allergic to soy ,
anything that has egg in it , uh , gluten ,
and if I eat a cashew , I could realistically die .
Holy shit .
Is there a password or something ?
I 'm sorry .
The new kid .
Ben ?
Yeah .
Oh , my God .
[ Ben ] Oh , my God .
- It 's been so long . - [ Beverly chuckles ]
[ Young Beverly ] Stay cool , Ben from soc class .
[ Young Ben ] You too , Beverly .
[ Young Beverly ] Hang tough , new kid on the block .
[ Richie ] Wow .
You two look amazing .
What the fuck happened to me ?
- What 's going on , man ? - [ Ben ] Hey , man .
- It 's Richie . Hi . - Yeah . It 's Ben .
[ both laughing ]
- Hi . - Hey .
[ gong rings ]
This meeting of the Losers ' Club
has officially begun .
Look at these guys .
[ mouths ] Ben .
[ all cheering ]
So , wait , Eddie , you got married ?
Yeah , why 's that so fucking funny , dickwad ?
What ? To , like , a woman ?
- Fuck you , bro . - [ Richie laughing ]
Fuck you !
All right . What about you , Trashmouth ? You married ?
There 's no way Richie 's married .
No , I got married .
- Richie , I don 't believe it . - When ?
- Did you not hear this ? - [ Eddie ] No .
You didn 't know I got married ?
- No . - Yeah , no . Me and your mom
are very , very happy right now .
- [ all laughing ] - [ Beverly ] Yeah , very happy .
- [ Bill ] He totally fell for it ! - Thanks .
[ laughing continues ]
Fuck you .
She 's very sweet . Sometimes , she 'll put her arm around me ,
and she 'll whisper to me , she 'll go ...
[ imitates Jabba the Hutt speaking alien language ]
We all get it . My mom was a great , big , fat person .
Shh .
Hilarious . Hysterical .
[ laughing continues ]
[ Richie ] Yeah , it 's a nice watch .
Wait , let 's talk about the elephant not in the room ...
Ben .
What the fuck , man ?
Okay , okay . Obviously , I lost a few pounds .
- [ Richie ] Lost a few pounds ? - [ Eddie ] Yeah , no shit you lost
- a few pounds . - You 're , like ... You 're hot !
[ Eddie ] That 's true .
[ Richie ] No , you 're like every Brazilian soccer player
wrapped up into one person . Gorgeous .
Leave him alone . You 're embarrassing him .
Okay , okay , all right . Please , come on .
Is Stanley coming or what ?
Someone save me .
Stan .
Stan Uris . Stan Urine .
Stanley Urine . No , no , he 's a fucking pussy .
He 's not gonna show .
Why would Stanley save you , anyway ?
Was I not the one who basically
performed surgery on you
- after Bowers cut you up ? - Yes !
Holy shit ! That 's right .
Please tell me you ended up becoming a doctor , Eds .
No , I ended up becoming a risk analyst .
[ Richie ] Oh , that sounds really interesting .
What does that entail ?
Yeah , so I work for a big insurance firm and ...
[ Richie imitates snoring ]
[ all laughing ]
Fuck you , dude . Fuck you .
Was this job invented before fun ?
- That 's so not funny . - [ Richie ] It is funny .
What the fuck are you laughing at ?
I propose a toast
to the Losers .
[ all protest ]
[ lively chattering ]
Let 's take our shirts off and kiss !
[ all ] Oh !
- Oh , here we go . - [ Eddie ] Thank you .
Thank you .
Like , Rogan-Marsh , half my wife 's closet Rogan-Marsh ?
That 's ... [ laughs ] That 's huge .
That 's our line . Me and my husband , Tom .
How long have you been married ?
Hey , we saw your movie ,
- by the way . - [ Bill ] You did ?
[ Beverly ] Oh , my God ! It was so good .
- [ Bill ] Oh , my God . - It was so scary .
And the ending sucked ?
[ chuckles ]
Yeah , it did . I 'm sorry .
That 's all right .
What ?
Nothing . This is just weird .
[ Beverly ] Yeah .
Just all this , all these memories ,
people that I don 't even remember forgetting .
I mean , it 's weird , right ?
Now that we 're all here ,
everything just comes back faster and faster .
I mean , all of it .
Yeah .
Yeah , you know , when Mike called me , I threw up .
Isn 't that weird ? Like , I got nervous .
I got , like , sick and I threw up .
[ Richie chuckles ]
I feel fine now .
I feel very relieved to be here with you guys .
Why is everybody looking at me like this ?
When Mike called me , I crashed my car .
- Seriously ? - [ Eddie ] Yeah .
[ Ben ] Shit , man , I hear you .
I mean , my heart was literally
pounding right out of my chest .
- I thought it was only me . - [ Bill ] It was like pure ...
[ Bill stuttering ]
Fear .
It 's fear . What you felt .
Why did we all feel like that , Mike ?
You remember something we don 't , don 't you , Mike ?
Something happens to you when you leave this town .
The farther away , the hazier it all gets .
But me , I never left .
So , yeah .
I remember .
I remember all of it .
Pennywise .
Oh , the fucking clown . [ breathes heavily ]
- Oh , shit . - [ Richie ] Pennywise .
Mike , you said you wanted our help with something .
What was that ?
There 's an echo here in Derry
that bounces back every 27 years .
What are you talking about ?
Hold on . Listen , listen .
We thought we stopped It back then .
We thought It was done , but ...
[ Richie ] Mike .
- [ whimpers ] - A week ago , a man ,
Adrian Mellon , slaughtered .
A girl , Lisa Albrecht , the other night , went missing .
[ Bill ] All right .
There 've already been others , and there will be more .
[ Richie ] I don 't want to hear about this shit .
- More death . More pain . - Calm down .
Let 's get another drink .
Let him explain . Let him explain .
Explain it to us , Mike .
That echo ,
we might have changed It ,
just like It changed us .
But we didn 't stop It .
Because It just bounced back .
We made an oath .
That 's why I brought you back . That 's why you 're here .
To finish It .
For good .
Well , that shit got dark fast .
Thanks , Mike .
My fortune cookie just says " Could . "
They don 't know how to do fortune cookies here .
Mine just says " Guess . "
You wanna throw that over here ?
[ Bill exhales deeply ]
What you got , Mikey ?
[ inhales shakily ]
[ Eddie ] Wait , what ?
[ Mike ] This is what I 'm talking about .
[ Richie ] " Guess . Cut . Not . Could . It . "
It 's a message .
[ Richie ] No , " Guess it could not cut . "
[ Eddie ] Why would it guess it could not cut ?
[ Ben ] Cut what ?
[ Richie ] " Guess it could not cut . "
" It " goes in front . There .
" It could not guess . "
- It couldn 't guess . - [ Richie ] " Could it ... "
No . " Could it not cut . "
When it says " It , " is it talking about It ?
- Yeah . All right . - [ Eddie ] Is that what it means ?
- Is " It " It ? - Where does this go ?
That 's what I 'm talking about .
It ... It could ...
[ Richie ] I don 't know what it fucking means !
You fuck with the fortune cookies , Mike ?
- No . - Whoa . Let him speak , man .
This is not me . This is what It does .
[ Eddie ] I need my fucking inhaler !
[ Richie ] What is wrong with you , man ? Why 'd you call us ?
- This is not fucking funny ! - [ Eddie ] This is so not funny !
- [ Bill ] Beverly ? - This is so not funny .
[ breathing shakily ]
[ men gasp ]
[ Eddie ] Why does it say Stanley ?
Someone else fucking answer me !
[ fortune cookies rattling ]
Holy shit .
What the fuck is that , man ?
Oh , my God .
Whoa , whoa !
[ crying ]
- Whoa ! - [ whimpering ]
Whoa , whoa , whoa !
Shit .
Hey ! Hey !
That fortune cookie 's looking at me ! Shit !
[ yelping ]
I don 't want to be here . I can 't fucking do this .
I wanna go home ! I don 't wanna be here !
I don 't wanna be here !
Holy shit !
Hey ! God damn it .
[ panicked chattering ]
[ both screaming ]
Hey , Eddie !
[ bleating ]
[ screaming ]
[ yelps ]
Whoa ! Fuck !
It 's not real !
[ screeches ]
This isn 't real ! It 's not real !
It 's not real ! It 's not real !
[ waitress ] Is everything all right ?
Yeah , yeah . Could we get the check ?
That 's what Pennywise does , right ?
He fucks with us . So , Stanley 's probably fine .
Hey , Mike . Do you have Stan 's number ?
Yeah .
[ boy ] Hey , Richie .
[ Richie ] How 'd you ...
How 'd you know my name ?
The fun 's just beginning .
Right ?
What he said , is it ...
Listen . You think this is funny ?
All right ?
Think this is some sort of game , huh ?
Well , fuck you , all right ?
[ Bill ] Rich , be careful , dude .
Fuck you ! I 'm not afraid of you !
" The fun 's just beginning . "
The line from your act , dude . I 'm a fan .
- Are those your parents ? - Yeah .
You want a picture ?
- You okay , Dean ? Come on . - I think I 'm good .
[ Richie ] Okay , cool . He 's a good kid .
Jesus , Richie . You don 't remember a line
from your own show ?
I don 't write my own material .
I fucking knew it ! I fucking knew it !
Hello , Mrs. Uris . My name 's Beverly Marsh .
I apologize for calling ,
but I 'm an old friend of your husband 's .
You lied to us . That 's not okay .
Yeah , first words out of your mouth should have been like ,
" Hey , man . You want to come to Derry and get murdered ? "
' Cause then I would have said no .
Guys .
[ Richie ] Fucking entrapment , man .
[ Patty on phone ] Oh ...
[ Patty sighs tearfully ]
He passed .
[ Beverly ] When did it happen ?
Yesterday .
It was horrible , the way he died .
His wrists .
- In the bathtub . - In the bathtub .
I 'm sorry . I have to go .
[ Beverly ] We 're all very sorry , Patty .
Thank you .
Stanley .
Pennywise knew . He knew before we did .
We have to stop him . I have a plan .
[ Richie ] I got a plan . Getting the fuck out of Dodge
before this ends worse than one of Bill 's books .
Who 's with me ?
We made a promise to each other .
Let 's un-make the promise .
Richie , other people are gonna die .
Other people die every day , man !
We don 't owe this town shit !
Plus , I just remembered I grew up here , like , two hours ago .
So , I 'm fucking leaving . Fuck this .
[ Eddie ] I 'm sorry , man , I 'm with Richie .
- Eds , please . - Listen .
What ? We stay , we die , that 's it ?
I 'm gonna go back to the inn , I 'm gonna pack up my shit ,
and I 'm gonna drive to my home .
- I 'm sorry , man . Good luck . - [ car engine starting ]
No , Eddie . Please . Please , Eddie !
Eddie , wait !
You okay ?
I 'm gonna head back to the Town House , too .
- Are you coming ? - Yeah .
You should have told us , Mikey .
Bill . Please , man .
I 'm begging you . Please .
Just listen to me , man . Please .
What are you gonna say ?
What could you possibly say
that would make any kind of a difference ?
They 're all gone .
Come on . Let me show you something .
One thing . And if you want to leave , you can leave .
Just let me show you this first . Please .
[ spectators cheering ]
[ boy ] Lapskew ! What kind of name is that , huh ?
My mom swings better than you !
How many times do I have to ...
She doesn 't even play baseball ! You suck !
Mommy , how much longer ?
Victoria , we came to watch the game .
We 're gonna watch the game .
[ spectators chanting ]
[ gasps ]
Hello , Vicky .
Isn 't that what your friends call you ?
Vicky ?
How did I know that ?
I guess I must be your friend , too . [ laughs ]
If you 're my friend , why are you hiding in the dark ?
You 're not my friend . You 're scary .
[ Pennywise crying ]
Why are you crying ?
People always make fun ' cause of the way I look .
I thought if you couldn 't see my face ,
then maybe you 'd want to be my friend .
Never mind . [ sobs ]
Oh , silly old Pennywise , you 'll never have no friends .
People make fun of me , too .
They do ?
' Cause of this .
Well , isn 't that silly ?
That little thing ?
Why , I can blow that thing right away .
You could ?
Oh , yes !
One poof and it 'd be gone ! [ giggles ]
You would have to get close enough to see my face .
I don 't know , Vicky .
No , it 's okay . I won 't make fun . I promise .
Promise promise ?
Well , okie-dokie !
Just come on in a little closer ,
and we 'll blow it away on the count of three ! [ giggles ]
[ giggles ]
One ,
two ...
You 're supposed to say three .
[ spectators cheering ]
[ music playing on video ]
[ John laughing ]
[ John sighs ]
[ man shuddering ]
[ door buzzes ]
Holy fuck .
Boo !
- [ yelps ] - [ laughing ]
Fuck yeah !
Hey , Hockstetter .
- Let 's go ! [ whooping ] - [ tires screeching ]
Let 's get our shit and get the fuck out of here .
Did you leave your stuff here ?
No , my stuff 's still in the car .
[ door closes ]
- Tell me . - Tell you what ?
Whatever it is you 're afraid to tell me right now .
Bev . Bev .
Back at the Jade when you were on the phone with Stanley 's ...
Stop .
She told you that she found him in the bathtub ,
but , Bev , I saw you .
I heard it . You said it first .
Whatever you guys are talking about ,
let 's make it happen faster , all right ? We gotta go .
Eduardo , andale ! Let 's go !
There 's something you 're not telling us .
You knew how Stanley died . You knew .
Wait , what ?
I can 't do this .
She knew how Stanley was going to die ,
is that what she just said ?
You can 't just walk away from this .
- [ bell dinging ] - How did you know
where he killed himself ?
Bev .
Talk to me .
Just talk to me . Like we used to .
Come on , how did you know ?
Because I saw it .
I 've seen all of us die .
[ bags thumping ]
Okay , I just got to grab my toiletry bag ,
and then we can go .
[ bags thud ]
What 'd I miss ?
[ Bill ] The library ?
- [ Mike ] Mmm-hmm . - [ Bill gasps ]
Wow .
Didn 't this place used to be bigger ?
Yo ! [ stutters ] Mike , where are you going ?
Mike , you live here ?
Yeah . Make yourself at home .
[ fridge door opens ]
- You want some water ? - [ Bill ] Yeah , sure .
[ water pouring ]
You see , memory 's the thing .
It 's the key .
It 's the key to everything .
If It really does want us [ stutters ] back here ,
don 't you think the smartest thing we can do
is just get the hell out of Derry ?
No , no , no . It does want us back .
Of course It does !
But It doesn 't know I know what I know .
What do you know ?
How to kill the shit out of It !
I 've read every book .
I 've talked to every person in this godforsaken town ,
everybody that would talk to me , anyway ,
and that 's not a long list .
But it wasn 't enough .
I had to know how this all started .
How It started .
And It started
- here . - Whoa .
- What am I looking at , Mike ? - It 's an artifact .
Early 18th century Shokopiwah .
Shoko ... How 'd you get it ?
I found it , in the ...
No , no , they gave it to me .
I stole it .
You stole it ?
- From Native Americans ? - Uh ...
- It 's complicated . - Yeah , it is .
They helped me on my journey .
So beautiful .
They showed me things . A vision .
Ow .
Holy fuck .
I feel kind of funky .
Hot .
Am I sweating ?
I need you to see what they showed me , Bill .
[ echoing ] Bill .
They live outside of Derry .
Beyond It 's reach .
They moved there many years ago .
Their holy man ,
their holy of holies ,
he took me in .
[ speaking native language ]
[ Mike in English ] Fed me their sacred Maturin .
I started to ... To react .
All living things must abide by the laws
of the shape they inhabit .
[ screaming ]
[ Mike ] While I sat there , looking out over the valley ,
I saw It arrive .
I knew that one day , I would have to make you all see .
Mike ,
did you put something in my drink ?
It 's , uh ...
It 's a root .
You ... [ stutters ]
You drugged me ? You drugged me ?
No , it 's a root with properties .
It 's just a micro-dose of what the Shokopiwah gave me ...
Why would you do that ?
... to open my eyes .
I don 't feel real good .
I need you to look ,
and you 'll see .
[ Bill ] I don 't feel good .
[ Mike ] Open your eyes .
Open your eyes .
They showed me the past .
[ yelps ]
Showed me the way It appeared to them .
[ whimpering ]
[ screams ]
They showed me their pain .
[ both screaming ]
They showed me how to stop It !
[ Native Americans chanting in native language ]
[ Bill breathing heavily ]
It 's over .
It 's over . You 're okay .
You 're okay . Did you see it ?
The ritual ?
- The Ritual of Chud ? - Yeah , I knew you ...
I knew you would see it .
I saw the whole fucking thing , Mike .
That 's how we kill It .
How are we going to do it ?
Everybody already [ stuttering ] said no .
But with you ,
they 'll listen .
This won 't work without all of us .
Okay . So , what do you mean that you 've seen us all die ?
Yeah , ' cause I gotta be honest .
That 's a fucked-up thing to just drop on somebody .
Every night since Derry ,
I 've been having these nightmares .
People in pain . People dying .
People ...
[ Eddie ] So , you have nightmares .
I have nightmares . People , they have nightmares .
But that doesn 't mean that your visions are true .
I 've watched every single one of us ...
[ Bill ] You 've seen every single one of us what ?
At the place that Stanley wound up .
That 's how we end .
Okay , how come the rest of us aren 't seeing that shit ?
I mean , what makes her so different ?
The Deadlights .
She was the only one of us
that got caught in the Deadlights that day .
We were all touched by It .
Changed .
Deep down . Like an infection . Or a virus .
A virus . You understand .
Slowly growing .
That virus , it 's been growing for 27 years .
This whole time , metastasizing .
It just got to Stan first , because ...
He was the weakest .
Jesus Christ , Rich .
Just saying what everyone else is thinking , man .
I mean , Rich , come on .
What Beverly sees , it will come to pass .
It 's what 'll happen to all of us , eventually ,
unless we stop It .
How the hell are we supposed to do that ?
The Ritual of Chud .
The Shokopiwah .
The first ones who fought It , they have a saying .
" All living things must abide by
" the laws of the shape they inhabit . "
A tribal ritual ?
Are you fucking kidding me , man ?
All right , there 's gotta be another way .
Okay ? This thing comes back , what , every 27 years ?
Let 's just kick the can down the road and do it then .
Wait , we 'll be 70 years old , asshole .
[ Beverly ] It doesn 't work that way .
None of us make it another 20 years ,
and the way it happens ...
So , if we don 't beat It this cycle , then ...
We die .
Horribly .
Yeah , I don 't need the " horribly " part .
I didn 't say it . She said it . Not me .
[ Bill ] All right , guys . Look .
I 've seen [ stuttering ] what he 's talking about ,
and it 's all true .
It 's the only way .
If we want this ritual to work ...
We have to remember .
Remember what ?
[ wind blowing ]
[ Mike ] It 's better if I show you .
We don 't have much time .
His cycle will end soon .
And once it does ...
[ Eddie ] We 're fucked .
[ Beverly ] The Barrens .
This is where we came .
After the rock fight .
The clubhouse .
You built that for us .
Yeah , the hatch has got to be around here someplace .
[ Eddie ] You did . I do remember that !
- Oh ! - Whoa ! Whoa !
You okay ?
[ Beverly laughs ]
- What ? - Nothing , it 's just ...
You haven 't changed .
It 's a good thing .
[ both chuckle ]
You know what ? I actually think the door was more like
around ...
[ crashing ]
Found it .
I 'm okay !
Come down !
What the dick is this ?
How 'd you build it ?
When did you build it ?
Here and there , I guess .
It was already dug out from something ,
so I just had to reinforce the walls
and get some wood for the roof door ,
and that 's pretty much it .
Pretty good for my first time , huh ?
[ Young Stanley yelps ]
[ Young Richie ] Now , that 's a cool feature .
What happens when you put your hand
on the other pillar , professor ?
Okay , you see , this is exactly why there are safety codes ,
why we have permits .
This place is a death trap . You understand that ?
Well , it 's a work in progress . Okay , Eddie ?
Just so you know , I get hurt , you are liable .
And , also , what is this ? The switch of an iron maiden ?
That 's a flashlight .
What is that , a horse hitch ?
When do you have horses down ...
Oh , this is cool .
That was like , three dollars ,
so be careful with that , please .
I have one of these . Hey , Stan , you see this ?
Yeah , okay , can you maybe not ?
Maybe not what ? Yeah , yeah , hold on . Maybe not what ?
Be awesome and have fun
and celebrate the magic of the paddle-ball ?
Wow .
Oh , good going , fucknut . You broke his thing .
- I broke it ? - Yeah ,
you broke it with your face .
What ?
[ Young Eddie ] I 'm not putting my fucking hand down there .
[ blows ]
[ Eddie ] Oh , man . That 's so cool .
[ Bill ] Oh , my God .
[ Eddie ] How do we all not remember that this was here ?
[ Richie as Pennywise ] Hey , Losers .
Time to float .
[ laughing ]
- Ahh ! - Fuck , Richie .
- Dude ! - Remember when he used to say
that shit ? And he 'd do that little dance .
[ vocalizing ]
Am I the only one who remembers this shit ?
Are you gonna be like this the entire time we 're home ?
All right . Just trying to add some levity to this shit .
I 'll go fuck myself .
[ whistling ]
It smells so fucking terrible in here .
Hey , you guys ?
[ stuttering ] This says " Stan . "
" For the use of Losers only . "
Bill .
- [ ' 80s music playing ] - The fuck is this ?
So you don 't get spiders stuck
in your hair when you 're down here .
Stanley , we 're not afraid of fucking spiders .
I stand corrected .
[ laughs ] That 's a first .
Touche .
Hey , Rich , your ten minutes are up .
What are you talking about ?
The hammock . Ten minutes each was the rule .
- I don 't see any sign . - [ Young Eddie ] Are you
being this way right now ? Really ? No , no , no .
Why would there be a sign if it was a verbal agreement ?
And I remember you agreeing on the fucking rule !
[ both grunting ]
[ Young Richie ] I can see your vagina !
[ Young Eddie ] Ten minutes each .
[ Young Richie ] Go back in your dumb little corner !
I fucked your mom !
[ Young Eddie ] No , you didn 't . Take that back !
You 're awfully good at this , new kid .
You really think so ?
There 's actually a summer program in Bar Harbor .
Teaches you , like , everything about architecture .
I was thinking about applying .
[ Young Richie ] I 'll do that .
I 'll do anything to get the hell out of Derry .
Man , when I graduate , I 'm going to Florida .
What 's in Florida , Mike ?
I don 't know .
You know , I guess it 's just a place I always wanted to go .
Stan , you should go with Mike to Florida .
You already act 80 .
You 'd clean up with all the grandmas . [ imitates kissing ]
[ all laughing ]
Do you guys think we 'll still be friends ?
When we 're older ?
[ Young Richie ] What ?
Why wouldn 't we be ?
Do any of your parents still hang out
with their friends from middle school ?
I mean , things might be different then .
We all might be different .
We 'll always still be friends .
I don 't think that just , you know ,
[ stuttering ] goes away because we get older .
[ Young Beverly ] Yeah , Stan . Come on .
You don 't have to be so ...
Sad .
He was old before his time .
[ Eddie ] Yeah .
I wonder what he was like all grown up .
Probably what he was like as a kid .
The best .
Here .
All right , Mike . What are we doing here ?
The ritual .
To perform it requires a sacrifice .
- Sacrifice ? I nominate Eddie . - Wait , what ?
Because you 're little . You 'll fit on a barbeque .
I 'm 5 '9 " . It 's , like , average height in most of the world .
It 's not that kind of a sacrifice , guys .
Mike ?
The past is buried .
But you 're gonna have to dig it up .
Piece by piece .
And these pieces ,
these artifacts ,
that 's why we 're here .
They are what you 'll sacrifice .
And since Stan isn 't here to find his ...
I figured we should all be here together
to find his artifact .
I think Bill just did that .
Okay , Mike , so where do we find our tokens ?
Yeah , I gotta be honest , man . All due respect .
This is fucking stupid , all right ?
Why do we need tokens ? All right ?
We already remember everything .
Saving Bev , defeating It ...
I mean , we 're caught up !
It 's not everything .
We fought . But what happened after that ?
Before the house on Neibolt .
Think .
[ stuttering ] We can 't remember , can we ?
See , there 's more to our story .
What happened that summer .
And those blank spaces ,
like pages torn out of a book .
That 's what you need to find .
We need to split up .
You each need to find your artifact .
Alone . That 's important .
When you do ,
meet me at the library tonight .
[ Eddie ] Yeah , I gotta say ,
statistically speaking , you look at survival scenarios ,
we 're gonna do much better as a group .
Yeah , splitting up would be dumb , man .
Okay , we gotta go together . All right ?
We were together that summer , right ?
[ Bill ] No .
Not that [ stutters ] whole summer .
[ Young Bill ] Take it back .
- [ groans ] - [ Young Beverly ] Bill !
You 're just a bunch of losers .
Fuck off !
- Fucking ... - Stop !
We were all together when we hurt It .
That 's why we 're still alive .
Yeah ? Well , I plan to keep it that way .
[ Young Beverly ] I bet by tomorrow ,
we 'll all be back together .
[ stutters ] I don 't think so .
Well , if we 're gonna stop It , we better be .
Maybe Richie was right .
Maybe we shouldn 't do anything about It , or maybe we can 't .
Okay , don 't let them get to you .
It 's a little late for that .
You should go .
Before your dad sees .
[ doorbell rings ]
Yes ?
Sorry . I ...
May I help you ?
I thought I rang Marsh .
Marsh ?
Alvin Marsh ?
My father .
I grew up here .
Dear ,
it 's not for me to tell you this ,
but your father passed away .
I 'm so sorry . You didn 't know ?
We hadn 't spoken in a while .
Well , won 't you come in ?
Let me offer you something to drink .
No , it 's fine . I have to go .
It 's the least I can do .
Sure . Okay .
[ door closes ]
Is it like you remember ?
Cleaner .
Well , you feel free to look around
while I get the water boiling .
Oh , really , it 's fine . You don 't need to do that .
Don 't be so polite .
[ Mr. Marsh ] Today is her birthday .
I can still smell her perfume .
And she 'd still be alive if it wasn 't for you .
Mama was sick .
You know that 's why she did what she did .
She did what she did
because she was embarrassed to be your mother .
You look like her .
But you are nothing like her .
Come here .
I said come here !
Close your eyes .
[ sniffing ]
You know that I would never hurt you .
You know that , don 't you ?
[ sobbing ] I 'm sorry . I 'm sorry .
You 'll always be my little girl , won 't you ?
Always .
[ laughs ]
" Your hair is winter fire ,
" January embers ...
" My heart burns there , too . "
- [ music playing ] - There . I do apologize .
It gets so very hot here this time of year .
It 's fine .
Well , you feel like you could just about die .
But you know what they say about Derry .
" No one who dies here ever really dies . "
[ clock ticking ]
But tell me , how is it being back in Derry ?
It 's good . Strange .
Strange ?
Oh , my .
Strange , how ?
- [ oven timer dings ] - [ Mrs. Kersh ] Oh .
I had some cookies in the oven before you came .
You stay right there .
I really ... I shouldn 't impose ... I 'm gonna ...
No , no , no . I insist .
[ record skipping ]
Mrs. Kersh , are these your family ?
Yes , dear .
My father came to this country with $ 14 in his pocket .
And he didn 't ask for a handout
the way that people come in here these days .
You know what he did ?
What did he do , Mrs. Kersh ?
My father joined the circus .
[ music becomes distorted ]
I was always Daddy 's little girl .
What about you ?
[ Pennywise ] Are you still his little girl , Beverly ?
[ Beverly breathing heavily ]
Are you ?
[ stomping footsteps approaching ]
[ growling ]
[ Beverly yelping ]
Mustn 't lie to our father !
[ Mrs. Kersh cackling ]
Help !
[ Pennywise ] Run , run , run .
Run , run .
You haven 't changed anything yet .
You haven 't changed their futures .
You ... You haven 't saved any of them .
Close your eyes , Bev .
Fuck you !
If you don 't believe ,
close them
and see !
[ laughing evilly ]
[ screaming ]
Come on , you . Come on .
[ Connor ] Ken , you little bitch ...
Yes !
You 're fucking good .
[ electronic voice ] Game over .
- Ah , well , I gotta go . - Hey !
Um ...
How about we go again ?
Play some more , you know ?
[ Belch ] Fuck you , man .
Only if you want to .
Dude , why are you being weird ?
I 'm not your fucking boyfriend .
Whoa , I ... I didn 't ...
What the fuck 's going on here ?
You assholes didn 't tell me
your town is full of little fairies .
[ Young Henry ] Richie fucking Tozier ?
What ? You 're trying to bone my little cousin ?
Get the fuck out of here , faggot !
Fucking move !
[ panting ]
[ crying ]
[ Pennywise ] Want a kiss , Richie ?
[ breathing heavily ]
[ rustling ]
- [ gasps ] - [ roaring ]
[ screaming ]
[ Young Richie grunts ]
[ laughing evilly ]
It 's not real . It 's not real . It 's not real . It 's not real .
I think I just shit my pants .
[ exhales ]
[ cheerleaders chanting ]
- [ Adrian ] Canal Days Festival . - Shit .
Closing performance is tonight .
Hope to see you there , handsome .
[ Pennywise ] Did you miss me , Richie ?
Oh , fuck !
' Cause I 've missed you .
No one wants to play with the clown anymore .
Play a game with me , would ya ?
How about Street Fighter ?
Oh , yes . You like that one , don 't you ?
[ Pennywise grunts ]
Or maybe Truth or Dare ?
Jesus .
Oh , you wouldn 't want
anyone to pick " truth , " though , would ya , Richie ?
You wouldn 't want anyone to know what you 're hiding .
[ Pennywise laughing ]
♪ I know your secret ♪
♪ Your dirty , little secret ♪
♪ Oh , I know your secret ♪
[ whimpering ]
Should I tell them , Richie ?
This isn 't happening . This isn 't real .
It isn 't real . It isn 't happening . It isn 't real .
- [ taunting playfully ] - [ screams ]
[ Pennywise grumbling ]
Come back and play !
[ distorted ] Come back and play with the clown !
- [ horn honking ] - Whoa !
- I 'm so sorry . Sorry . - [ driver ] Watch it , you jerk !
Sorry .
[ laughing shakily ]
[ laughing ]
Oh , man !
- [ shopkeeper ] Can I help you ? - Hi .
Yeah , I want to see about the ... [ stuttering ]
Baseball card ?
The bowling ball ?
No , the ... [ stuttering ]
- Banjo ? - [ chord plays ]
- Beaver ? - [ chitters ]
Fucking bike .
You wanna use that kind of language ,
take it out in the street .
I 'm sorry .
Can we just start over and pretend that I just walked in ?
How can I help you ?
Thank you . Yes . I want to buy the bike .
Aren 't you William Denbrough , the writer ?
Yeah , that 's ...
That 's me .
That bike used to be mine .
Well , it 's mine now .
But you 're the big author .
You want it , you can afford it .
[ chuckles ]
All right . How much ?
$ 300 .
You can afford it .
I 'll get it .
[ Bill ] I guess that 's kind of a deal .
You ... You want me to sign it for you ?
Nah .
I didn 't like the ending .
[ Bill ] Uh ...
Three big ones .
- All yours . - Uh-huh .
I don 't know how fast she 'll go .
Been there a lot of years .
[ Bill ] You know what , mister ?
She was fast enough to beat the devil .
- [ metal clanging ] - [ groaning ]
[ panting ]
Come on .
[ yelps ]
[ laughing ] Yeah , I missed you , too .
Yeah !
Whoo !
Hi-ho , Silver !
Away !
[ children 's laughter echoing ]
Bye , Billy !
I know you 're down there .
I know you [ stuttering ] can hear me .
There 's something I have to know .
All of the kids in this town you could have taken ,
why [ stuttering ] Georgie ?
Say something !
Why him ?
[ shouting ] Why him ? Why him ? Why him ?
[ sobbing ]
[ Pennywise ] Why ?
Because you weren 't there , Billy .
[ Pennywise laughing evilly ]
[ Georgie ] Billy , don 't leave .
Hello ?
Billy .
I 'm still here .
Help me .
Georgie .
Georgie ?
Help me , Billy .
Take my hand .
I 've got you , buddy . Come on .
[ Georgie ] He 's coming .
Take my hand !
- I got you . Come on . - Billy , please . He 's coming .
- Take my hand . - Billy !
Come on , take my hand !
[ yelping ]
[ laughing ]
[ screaming ]
[ panting ]
[ childish laughing ]
I hate you !
I hate you .
[ Dean ] Who are you talking to ?
Move , move , move !
Move ! Move !
You hear voices from that sewer , you stay away from it .
You hear voices from the sewer ?
No .
No . Just stay away from that sewer .
I only hear voices in the tub .
You know . From the drain .
What kind of voices ?
Kids .
And other times , like a ...
Like a clown ?
You listen to me . You listen good .
You need to get out of this town .
All right ? Tell your parents . Make up a reason .
You make up a fucking lie . I don 't care what you do .
Just get out of this town . Make them
never bring you back . Do you understand ?
You leave Derry and you stay out of Derry !
Do you understand me ?
I 'm supposed to be at the festival .
Tell me you understand !
[ breathing heavily ]
I 'm supposed to be at the festival .
I gotta go .
Just be careful !
[ exhales ]
- [ school bell ringing ] - [ students chattering ]
[ boy ] Come on , let 's get the fuck outta here .
Wake up , fat-ass .
[ Young Ben groans ]
Fucking loser .
- [ sighs ] - [ door closes ]
[ Cover Girl playing on headphones ]
[ gasps ]
Whoa .
Easy . It 's just me .
What are you and your little buddies up to in here ?
Oh . Those guys are definitely not my buddies .
No , I meant your real friends .
Joey . Jonathan . Donnie . Danny .
- Oh . - [ turns walkman off ]
Are you smoking in school ?
Secret hideout .
Don 't tell anyone .
You okay , new kid ?
Yeah , no , I 'm fine .
I guess I 'm just worried
that we 're not all gonna be the same after the fight .
As long as we can still hang out , who cares ?
You really mean that ?
Well , yeah , of course , dummy .
You and me .
Oh , my God !
I meant as a friend .
You actually thought I could like someone
as fat and gross and disgusting like you ?
[ lighter clicking ]
No matter how many stupid poems
[ demonic voice ] you write .
[ gasps ]
" Your hair is winter fire .
" January embers .
" My heart burns there , too . "
[ panting ]
That 's not the real Beverly .
Beverly would never say anything like that .
She 'd never say that .
- [ screams ] - Kiss me , fat boy .
- [ yells ] - [ screams ]
[ panting ]
[ grunting ]
Oh , nobody wants to kiss the fat boy .
Just leave me alone .
Alone ?
Oh , you 've always been alone .
That 's not true . I have real friends .
Bill . Eddie . Mike . Stanley . Richie . Beverly .
They 're my real friends .
Kiss me as if it were the last time .
[ grunting ]
[ roars ]
[ janitor ] What the hell are you doing , kid ?
[ exhales ]
[ sniffling ]
[ door opens ]
Guys ?
[ Beverly ] Hey .
[ Ben ] Hey .
So , what did you see out there ?
Something I wish I hadn 't .
So , what , we just ...
We kill It , and then we just forget everything again ?
I hope so . Don 't you ?
I don 't know .
I guess I want to hold on to the good stuff , you know ?
Mmm .
Come on . There must be something from
the past that you don 't want to forget again .
I remember being scared shitless .
Cold .
I remember you guys in your tighty-whities .
Okay . Please forget that moment .
I remember this .
I remember the boy who wrote it for me .
Not him , so much ,
but how he made me feel .
And a kiss .
It 's still blurry , but I think the longer we 're here ,
the more I can see it .
The more I can see that moment .
The more I can see ...
Bill .
I think .
I don 't know . Do you remember ...
- [ door opens ] - Bev , um ...
- Move . Move . - [ Beverly ] What 's wrong ?
I 'm leaving .
[ Ben ] What ? You can 't leave , man .
We split , we all die .
Yeah , I 'll take my chances . We 're gonna die , anyway .
Rich . Um ...
Rich .
Hey , kids ! It 's Burrow the Beaver !
Come on down . It 's the last day
of the festival here at Canal Days .
[ upbeat music playing ]
Ahh !
Asshole !
[ Muzak playing ]
- [ ripping ] - Hello ?
[ sniffing ]
Can I help you ?
Yeah , I called in ...
I had prescription called in for Kaspbrak .
Kaspbrak ?
It 's an inhaler .
Uh ... Eddie Kaspbrak ?
Mmm-hmm . That 's me .
I remember you .
Yeah .
- Mmm-hmm . - How 's your mom ?
Oh , uh ... Well , she died a few years ago .
It 's very sad . It was from liver cancer .
What 's that ?
- What 's what ? - That .
- All right . - Uh-huh .
- Okay . - [ grunts ]
No , it 's not gonna pop . It 's a mole .
It might not be cancer .
Cancer ?
But it might be .
You just stay here .
I 'll get you something .
[ squeaking ]
Okay .
You came here for your stinky breath pills ?
[ stammers ] My breath is fine .
Thank you .
That 's not what my dad said .
He said you have a tumor .
On your dick .
[ laughs ]
But you don 't take pills for ...
Wait , what did your dad say ?
There you go .
I hope your dick feels better .
Thank you .
For the inhaler , not for the penis thing .
[ Mrs. Kaspbrak ] Eddie !
Eddie bear !
[ Young Eddie ] Mommy ?
[ Mrs. Kaspbrak ] Eddie bear !
[ yelps ]
Mommy ?
Eddie , come help me ! Quick !
[ gagging ]
[ inhales deeply ]
[ Mrs. Kaspbrak ] Eddie !
Mommy ?
Eddie ?
Eddie , help me !
Quick , help me !
Mommy ?
Eddie bear , come help me , quick !
[ glass shatters ]
[ Young Eddie gasps ]
[ yelping ]
[ screaming ]
[ Mrs. Kaspbrak ] Eddie ?
[ Young Eddie ] The fuck is she doing here ?
What is taking you so long ?
I don 't know . Why are you here ?
Mommy !
He 's coming ! You gotta get me outta here !
- Who 's coming ? - Eddie .
[ rustling ]
[ Young Eddie ] What the fuck is that ?
[ Young Eddie breathing heavily ]
- [ growls ] - [ Young Eddie whimpering ]
- Mommy . - You gotta get me outta here .
- [ growling ] - [ Mrs. Kaspbrak ] He 's coming !
He 's gonna kill me ! Eddie !
Help ! Please , help me ! He 's going to infect me !
Eddie ! He 's gonna infect me ! Eddie !
- [ Young Eddie grunts ] - Help me !
- [ Mrs. Kaspbrak whimpering ] - [ growling ]
Help me , Eddie ! He 's coming , Eddie !
- [ grunting ] - Eddie , hurry !
- He 's gonna infect me , Eddie ! - [ snarling ]
[ screaming ]
Oh , my God ! Eddie !
Hurry up , Eddie !
- [ snarling ] - [ screaming ]
Eddie !
[ both screaming ]
- [ Young Eddie ] I can 't do it ! - [ Mrs. Kaspbrak ] Eddie ! Eddie !
I 'm sorry , I can 't do it . [ screams ]
I knew you would leave me , Eddie ! [ sobbing ]
- [ both screaming ] - [ creature snarling ]
[ Mrs. Kaspbrak ] Eddie , help me !
[ Mrs. Kaspbrak screaming ]
[ screaming ]
[ Mrs. Kaspbrak ] Eddie !
[ Young Eddie sobbing ]
What 's all this shit doing here ?
Why is that curtain still here ?
Okay , all right .
Are you gonna do this , Eds ?
It 's just a memory .
It 's just a memory . You 're fine .
Deep breath . Deep breath .
Okay . You gonna do it ?
- [ roaring ] - [ screaming ]
Shit ! Oh , shit ! Oh , fuck !
[ Eddie yelping ]
Stop ! Stop !
[ choking ]
[ yelling ]
[ Eddie grunting ]
That 's right !
Fuck you !
[ Eddie choking ]
[ Angel of the Morning playing ]
[ screaming ]
What the fuck ?
[ whimpers ]
[ shouting indistinctly ]
[ gasps ] What ?
Push , don 't pull , you moron .
- Oh . [ laughs ] Thanks . - [ bells jingle ]
Oh , my God . What happened to you ?
Nothing . I 'm fine .
I 'm fine . Everything 's fine .
Hey , how you doing ? Where 's everybody else ?
Richie wants to leave .
Ben 's upstairs trying to get him to stay .
Eddie 's just scared .
So am I , Bill .
Aren 't you ?
We 're all scared .
That 's what worries me .
Because that 's what It wants .
We can do this ,
but we have to stick together .
[ object clattering ]
Should we be running ?
This is Derry . I 'm kinda getting used to it .
What does that mean ?
Shit . It 's the kid .
What ?
It 's the kid from the place .
The Chinese place .
I saw him on the way here .
He lives at my old house .
He was going to the fair , and ...
He 's going to the fair . I gotta help him .
Okay , okay . Listen to me . We 'll go together .
I 'm gonna get Richie and Ben and we 'll go .
There 's no time . I can 't let it happen again .
What happened before wasn 't your fault .
None of it was .
I wish that were true , Bev .
Bill ! Bev !
- What is this ? What happened ? - Uh ...
Did Bill just leave ?
I couldn 't stop him .
Everybody 's leaving .
It 's all right . It 's Bill . He 'll be back .
He 'll come back .
Well , at least I got Richie to stay .
Fuck . Oh .
[ car unlocks ]
[ engine starts ]
Oh . And then the leper , he threw up all over me .
" Hey , it 's Mike Hanlon .
" Why don 't you come back to Maine ? "
It 's your time , Eddie .
- [ yells ] - [ groans ]
[ muffled ] What ?
[ Henry laughing ]
Why ?
Why did you do that ?
Because he says it 's your time .
Who says it 's my time ? [ laughing ]
You know , Eddie .
- [ whimpering ] - You know .
Time to float .
[ both laughing ]
Where did he go ?
Now give me back my fucking knife !
[ groans ]
You should cut that fucking mullet .
It 's been , like , 30 years , man .
- [ groaning ] - [ Eddie ] Guys !
Oh , shit .
Eds ?
[ Beverly screaming ]
[ Ben ] Jesus , Eds . What the hell ?
- Bowers is in my room . - Oh , my ...
[ glass shattering ]
- [ Eddie ] Is it bad ? - [ Beverly ] No .
[ groans ]
[ Young Henry ] I 'm gonna carve my whole name
onto this cottage cheese !
- [ grunting ] - [ groaning ]
[ blows kiss ]
[ laughing ]
[ Henry ] One down !
Fuck yeah !
[ panting ]
[ children chattering ]
Hey !
Hey , kid ! Kid !
Whoa , whoa , whoa . I 'm so sorry . I 'm sorry .
Hey !
Excuse me . Excuse me . Hey ! Hey !
Whoa , whoa , whoa !
Fuck .
[ carnival music playing ]
[ spooky laughing ]
[ groans ] Fuck !
[ groaning ]
Kid ! Hey , kid ! [ groans ]
Fuck .
Kid ?
[ grunts ]
Hey !
[ grunting ]
Kid . [ groans ]
Kid ? Hey ! Hey !
Kid ! [ groans ]
- [ gasps ] - Fuck . [ groaning ]
Shit .
Hey .
What are you doing here ?
[ laughing ] Hey .
No , I 'm here to [ stutters ] help .
Stop following me !
I 'm gonna get you out of here .
[ squeaking ]
No .
Please .
[ Dean whimpering ]
Ah .
I 'm here this time . Just take me .
[ Pennywise groans ]
[ laughing ]
- [ groans ] - [ Bill yelps ]
- Son of a bitch ! - [ Pennywise laughing ]
- [ groans ] - [ whimpering ]
[ Pennywise laughing ]
- [ Bill grunting ] - [ Dean whimpering ]
[ screaming ]
Help !
[ Bill and Pennywise grunting ]
- [ panting ] - [ whimpering ]
[ yelling ]
- [ Dean screaming ] - [ Bill yelps ]
[ Bill panting ]
I should go back there . I just fucking
left them in the lurch , man . I should go back there .
What the fuck are you talking about ? Fuck that .
Fuck them .
I got dates in fucking Reno , man .
[ Young Stanley singing in Hebrew ]
[ congregants responding ]
[ Young Stanley ] Reflecting on the meaning of
what I just read ,
the word " Leshanot " comes up a lot ,
which means " to change , to transform . "
Which makes sense , I guess ,
because today I 'm supposed to become a man .
It 's funny , though .
Everyone , I think , has some memories
they 're prouder of than others , right ?
[ timer beeping ]
And maybe that 's why change is so scary .
' Cause the things we wish we could leave behind ...
- Good morning , Mike . - How you doing ?
... the whispers we wish we could silence ...
His pa is the one . The one that set that fire .
... the nightmares we most want to wake up from ,
the memories we wish we could change
the secrets we feel like we have to keep
are the hardest to walk away from .
The good stuff ?
The pictures in our mind that fade away the fastest ?
Those pieces of you it feels the easiest to lose .
- Maybe I don 't want to forget . - [ camera clicking ]
Maybe if that 's what today is all about ,
forget it , right ?
- Thank you , Stanley . - [ stammering ]
Today , I 'm supposed to become a man ,
but I don 't feel any different .
I know I 'm a loser .
And no matter what ,
- I always fucking will be . - [ congregants gasp ]
Thanks for showing up , Stanley .
[ Mrs. Hanlon ] Mike ! Help !
[ Mrs. Hanlon screaming ]
Help us !
- Please , Mikey , get help ! - [ Mr. Hanlon ] Help us !
Please , Mikey , get help !
- [ Mrs. Hanlon ] Mikey ! - [ both scream ]
[ Henry yelling ]
[ groans ]
[ laughing ]
You should have burned , Mike .
[ yelling ]
Just like your druggie parents .
- [ grunting ] - Can you see them yet ?
[ laughing ] Crisping ?
[ both grunting ]
Like fried fucking ...
[ groans ]
[ thuds ]
I guess you could say that was long overdue .
Get it ? ' Cause we 're in a library .
[ retches ] No .
Oh ...
[ Beverly ] Mike ?
- [ Ben ] Hey . - [ Beverly ] Hey . Oh , my God .
[ Beverly screams ]
[ Beverly panting ]
Are you all right ?
No , I 'm not all right . I just fucking killed a guy .
I was talking to Mike .
Where 's Bill ?
- [ cell phone ringing ] - [ clears throat ]
Bill , we 're all at the library .
Where are you at ?
[ stuttering ] He took a little kid , Mike .
He took a little kid right in fucking front of me .
No , no , no , no , no . Just , just ...
Look , just come here to the library .
We can talk about the plan .
- I 'm gonna go kill It . - No , no , no .
I don 't want any of you to get killed with me .
Bill ! Bill !
He 's going to fight It alone .
- What ? - [ Mike ] Alone .
It 's about the group .
The ritual doesn 't work without the group .
Doing it together is why it 'd work .
Mike , did he tell you where he was going ?
If he really wanted to kill Pennywise ,
there 's only one place he 'll go .
The same place the ritual needs to be performed .
Oh , we 're not gonna like this , are we ?
[ sighs ] Fuck .
[ breathing heavily ]
[ Beverly ] Bill !
No , no , you guys , no !
[ stuttering ] I started all this .
It 's my fault that you 're all here .
This curse , this fucking thing that 's inside you all .
It started growing the day
that I made you go down to the Barrens
because all I cared about was finding Georgie .
Now , I 'm gonna go in there ,
and I don 't know what 's gonna happen ,
but I can 't ask you to do this .
[ Beverly ] Well ,
we 're not asking you , either .
- Bev ... - We didn 't
do it alone then , Bill ,
so we 're not gonna do this alone now .
Losers stick together .
So , does somebody want to say something ?
Richie said it best when we were here last .
I did ?
- " I don 't want to die " ? - Not that .
" You 're lucky we 're not measuring dicks " ?
[ Bill ] No .
" Let 's kill this fucking clown " ?
Let 's kill this fucking clown .
[ Richie ] Hmm .
Well , I love what he 's done with the place .
Beep-beep , Richie .
All right .
Hey , hey . That 's the basement , right ?
[ groaning ]
[ Beverly ] Ben ?
[ Eddie ] No , no ! Hey , hey ! Ben !
[ both ] Ben !
Ben ? What 's wrong ?
[ continues groaning ]
- Ben ! - Okay . All right .
- [ Bill ] Ben ! - [ rattling ]
Okay , that can 't be good , right ?
- [ Ben continues groaning ] - [ Beverly gasping ]
Help ! Hey !
[ whimpers ]
[ pounding on fridge door ]
[ both ] Ugh !
It 's Stan .
- [ Ben screaming ] - [ whimpering ]
[ Beverly ] It can 't be real .
- [ yelling ] - Oh !
- [ all yelping ] - Oh , God .
Shit .
[ hyperventilating ]
I 'd still be alive if it wasn 't for you , Bill .
No .
- Beverly ! - [ screaming ]
[ Pennywise laughing ]
[ Ben whimpering ]
[ knife unsheathing ]
[ screaming ]
[ grunting ]
[ cracking ]
Richie , what 's happening to me ?
[ groaning ]
You gotta be fucking kidding .
[ laughing ]
[ yelps ] Fuck !
Oh , God damn it , get it away from me . Oh , God !
[ snarling ]
Whoa , whoa ! [ yelping ]
[ panting ]
- [ footsteps retreating ] - [ Pennywise laughing ]
Eddie .
Hey . Are you okay ?
I 'm ...
Oh , there he is .
[ screaming ]
Get it off of me !
- [ Bill grunting ] - [ continues screaming ]
[ Ben ] Richie !
- [ Mike ] Richie ! - Richie ! Hey !
- [ Bill grunting ] - [ Richie screaming ]
- [ Richie ] Get it off of me ! - I wanna go home .
Get the knife !
God damn it , Eddie , get the knife !
Bill ! Get it off of me , Bill ! Quick ! [ screaming ]
- Eddie , get the knife ! - [ grunts ]
Ahh ! Fuck !
- [ grunting ] - [ Young Stanley groaning ]
[ grunting ]
[ Bill grunts ]
[ panting ]
[ Beverly ] What ?
[ grunts ]
[ grunting ]
[ laughing ]
Is everybody okay ?
- [ coughing ] - [ Bill ] You all right ?
[ stuttering ] He could have fucking died , man .
You know that , right ?
I can 't see .
Georgie 's dead . The kid 's dead . Stanley 's dead .
You want Richie , too ? You want Richie , too ?
I don 't want Richie , too . I don 't . I don 't .
Please don 't be mad , Bill .
I was just scared . [ crying ]
That 's what he wants , right ?
Don 't give it to him .
A lot of memories , huh ?
All bad .
[ rats squeaking ]
[ Eddie ] Oh , man .
Blech . Gray water .
Shit . This is it .
This is where it happened .
No , no , no .
No . Ugh !
[ Pennywise ] Bevvie .
Bev , what is it ?
I thought I heard something .
- [ screaming ] - [ laughing ]
Bev !
Time to sink !
- [ laughs ] - [ screams ]
[ Mike ] Bev !
[ echoing ] Guys .
Okay , guys . Come on .
Hey , guys .
Guys , come on . [ crying ] Please , come on .
I don 't want to walk out of here alone .
[ all gasping ]
- You okay ? - [ Beverly crying ]
I feel like crying .
Mike . Where do we go from here ?
[ Mike ] In the depths is where It crept .
In the beneath , to find belief .
In the depths is where It crept .
Is he okay ?
I think at this point , that 's a relative question .
What 's on the other side ?
I don 't know . No one does .
[ Bill ] Whoa , whoa , whoa !
Mike .
- Mike , don 't . - All right .
- See you down there . - [ all ] Mike !
Wait ! [ stammers ]
- Stay together . - Okay .
You guys , I can 't do it .
I can 't . You saw what happened up there .
I was gonna let you die .
I just fucking froze up .
If you let me go down there with you ,
I 'm gonna get us all killed . [ inhales deeply ]
Hey , hey , hey . Give me that .
- Give me that . - Richie .
Let go , you little turd .
- Just let me get ... - [ inhaler spraying ]
[ inhales deeply ]
- I got it . - Stop .
Listen to me .
You had a moment . Fine .
But who killed a psychotic clown before he was 14 ?
Me .
Who stabbed Bowers with a knife
he pulled out of his own face ?
Also me .
Who married a woman 10 times his own body mass ?
- Me . - Yeah .
You 're braver than you think .
All right . Thanks , Rich .
- Ow . - Sorry .
[ Beverly ] Hey . Here .
Take it .
It kills monsters .
- Does it ? - Yeah .
If you believe it does .
Thanks , Bev .
[ Mike echoing ] You guys good ?
[ Bill ] Yeah .
Can you get through that ?
[ Mike ] It 's the only way . This way .
It 's in here !
Through here .
It 's tight , but we can get through .
This is where It hid .
So , all this has been under Derry , like , forever ?
Not forever .
Just a few million years .
It can only be attacked in its true form .
The ritual will show us that .
And what is It 's true form ?
I hope it 's a puppy .
Like a Pomeranian or ...
I 'll shut up .
It 's light .
A light that must be snuffed out by darkness .
Your artifacts .
Place them in the fire .
The past must burn with the present .
This is the boat that I built
with Georgie .
[ Eddie ] It 's my inhaler .
[ inhales deeply ]
Come on , dude .
Something that I wish I had held on to .
This is a page from my yearbook .
That only one person signed .
I probably should have forgotten it ,
but I couldn 't , because I kept it in my wallet
for 27 years .
This is a token from the Capitol Theater .
- You brought an actual token ? - [ Richie ] Yeah , man .
That 's what we were supposed to do , asshole .
Do you have any idea how long that 's gonna take to burn ?
Yeah , but so is your inhaler , dude .
Guys , come on .
All the toxic fumes and the plastic and shit , so ...
Look closely , Bev .
You see it ?
That 's where you hit Bowers .
The rock fight .
The day these bonds were forged .
That 's not gonna burn , either .
Oh , wait .
Couldn 't forget about Stan ,
again .
[ Mike ] Okay .
Grab hands .
Come on .
The Ritual of Chud .
It 's a battle of wills .
The first step was our reunion .
The second was the gathering of tokens .
This is the final step .
What the ...
Fuck is that ?
- [ Mike ] Don 't look at them ! - [ Eddie ] Are those
- the Deadlights ? - Don 't look at it !
Okay .
Turn light into dark . Turn light into dark . Say it !
- [ Eddie ] Say what ? - Say it !
[ all ] Turn light into dark .
[ Mike chanting in native language ]
[ others in English ] Turn light into dark .
Turn light into dark .
[ continues chanting in native language ]
[ others chanting in English ] Turn light into dark .
Turn light into dark . Mike , what 's happening , man ?
Keep chanting !
Turn light into dark .
[ Mike chanting in native language ]
[ others chanting in English ]
Turn light into dark !
Turn light into dark ! Turn light into dark !
- [ Mike ] Keep chanting ! - Turn light into dark !
[ Mike chanting in native language ]
[ Eddie ] Turn light into dark ! Turn light into dark !
Is it working ? Did we do it ?
[ box creaking ]
[ Mike grunting ]
What is this ? Is this part of it ?
Mike , is this supposed to be happening ?
- [ Eddie ] What ? No , no , no . - Keep chanting !
- What ? - Keep chanting !
Turn light into dark !
- Turn light into dark . - Come on !
[ all ] Turn light into dark . Turn light into dark .
- [ whimpering ] - Whoa !
[ gasps ]
Hey ! Hey !
[ all yelping ]
Shit !
Move , move ! Whoa !
[ groans ]
- [ high-pitched ringing ] - [ muffled shouting ]
Bev . Bev .
- [ Beverly ] Richie . - [ Richie ] Are you okay ?
- I can 't hear shit . - He 's okay .
- [ Bill ] Are you all right ? - [ Ben ] Yeah . No , no , no .
- [ Eddie ] Wait , where 's Mike ? - [ Ben ] Mike !
[ men ] Mike !
- I 'm here ! - [ Richie ] Hey , guys .
Did we do it ? Did we do it ? Yeah ? Did we do it ?
[ Richie ] We put the tokens in the thing .
That 's good , right ?
[ Eddie ] We did it , right ?
[ all exclaim in fear ]
Shit ! Shit !
Oh , did it work , Mikey ? Did it work ?
[ Pennywise laughing ]
Tell them why your silly little ritual didn 't work .
Tell them it 's all just a ...
What 's the word , Eds ?
Gazebo ?
Mike , what 's he talking about ?
[ stuttering ] Mikey ?
Oh , Mikey , you never showed them the fourth side , did you ?
[ Pennywise laughing ]
Didn 't want them to know
what actually happened to the poor Shokopiwah ?
- Yum , yum , yum , yum , yum . - [ rumbling ]
[ Shokopiwah screaming ]
Fuck , Mikey . You lied to us , again ?
[ stammering ] No , but they didn 't believe !
They didn 't believe they could kill It !
That 's why it didn 't work back then !
Are you fucking kidding me , Mike ?
- We hurt him . - Fuck !
[ Bill ] Fuck you , Mikey .
I needed something , anything , for us to remember .
Anything for us to believe !
- God damn it ! - Fuck !
[ Pennywise laughing ]
[ all screaming ]
[ Beverly ] The Deadlights !
Don 't look at them !
[ groans ]
For 27 years ,
I dreamt of you . [ laughing ]
I craved you .
Oh , I 've missed you ! [ laughs ]
Mike ! Move back !
Waiting for this very moment .
Mikey ! You gotta move , Mikey !
- Sorry . I 'm sorry , guys . - [ Eddie ] Mike , come on , man !
I 'm sorry . I 'm so sorry .
Time to float !
[ all gasp ]
- Oh , shit ! - Sorry .
[ Eddie ] Mike , come on , get up ! Get him up !
- [ Bill ] Go , go ! - [ Eddie ] Run !
- Oh , shit ! - [ Bill ] Run ! Go , go , go !
[ snarling ]
Go , go , go !
Go !
[ Ben ] Go , go , go !
Where 'd he go ?
Don 't worry . We 'll find a way out .
[ gasps ]
[ coughing ]
- Oh , shit ! - [ yelps ] Can he see us ?
- [ both screaming ] - Oh , my God !
[ Eddie ] Shit .
Oh , shit .
[ Richie ] Holy shit ! Holy shit ! Run !
[ Eddie ] Oh , shit !
[ both gasp ]
[ Richie ] Shit . You gotta be fucking kidding me .
We 're trapped .
- Where do we go ? - [ rumbling ]
[ both screaming ]
[ grunting ]
[ gasps ]
[ screaming ]
[ groaning ]
[ yelping ]
- [ Eddie ] God damn it ! - [ Richie ] Uh ...
All right . " Not Scary At All . " All right ?
No , no , no .
- [ stammering ] - Wait . Why ?
They 're flipped . He 's fucking with us .
- Are you sure ? Positive ? - Trust me .
- Yes ! - Okay .
[ woman ] Where 's my shoe ?
[ woman tap dancing ]
[ woman laughing ]
[ Eddie and Richie screaming ]
What the fuck ? You told me to trust you !
[ screaming continues ]
He 's not fucking with us .
Let 's go to " Not Scary At All . "
Okay . [ breathing heavily ]
It 's all right . Let 's go .
[ panting ]
Oh , shit .
No way am I falling for this shit again .
Oh , yeah . That thing 's a fucking monster .
Richie , make it sit .
I know your moves , you little bitch .
Rich ?
It 's gone , man .
- Yeah . Wait . - Oh . Okay .
Okay .
Sit .
[ Eddie ] He did it .
Oh , that 's cute .
- That 's a good boy . - That 's actually super cute .
That 's a good boy .
- Are you a good boy ? - [ Richie ] Good boy .
- [ snarling ] - [ both screaming ]
Shit !
Yo , next time , we just go with regular " Scary . "
Next time ?
[ Georgie ] I lost it , Billy .
It just floated off .
[ stuttering ] I 'm not mad at you .
It 's your fault what happened , isn 't it ?
You weren 't really that sick that morning , were you ?
No .
I just pretended
because I didn 't want to play with you .
I just didn 't want to .
You lied and I died .
You lied and I died !
It happened because of me , Georgie . Me .
No , no , no . It was ...
Lied and died !
- [ yelps ] - Lied and died !
[ muffled ] You lied and I died !
[ breathing heavily ]
[ suffocating ]
[ exhales shakily ]
[ pounding on door ]
[ yelps ]
You in there , you little shit ? I can smell you .
[ sniffs ] You smell just like Lois Lane .
Here 's Johnny !
[ voices chattering loudly ]
[ voice laughing sinisterly ]
[ liquid rushing ]
[ gasps ]
[ screaming ]
[ yelping ]
[ continues screaming ]
All that success ,
all those sit-ups ,
but deep down , still just
a little fat , fat , fatty loser ...
[ Pennywise laughing ]
... who always knew he would die alone .
[ screaming ]
[ hissing ]
- Slut ! - Bev !
[ screaming ]
Beverly !
Bevvie .
Just open up the door for me , okay ?
Beverly , can you hear me ?
[ grunting ]
Come to Daddy , now .
Bev , don 't listen !
[ yelps ]
Bev !
Are you still my little girl , Bevvie ?
[ gasping ]
Beverly , I love you !
Ben !
Are you still my little girl , Bevvie ?
Are you still my little girl ?
Not anymore !
- [ grunts ] - [ screaming ]
[ Mr. Marsh ] You little ...
" Your hair is winter fire .
[ whimpering ]
" January embers .
" My heart ...
[ shouting ]
No !
[ Ben screaming ]
Ben !
- [ continues screaming ] - Ben !
[ both grunting ]
[ Ben gasping ]
" January embers . "
" My heart burns there , too . "
It was you .
[ Pennywise whooping ]
We deserve to die .
No .
You were the best big brother there ever [ stuttering ] was .
No ! We killed our little brother !
[ Bill shushing ]
He loved you .
And just because you didn 't want to play
on a rainy day ,
just one time ,
that does not make it our fault .
[ gun clicks ]
[ chuckling ]
[ gun clicking ]
And it never ,
ever ...
[ breathing heavily ]
... did .
- [ gasps ] - [ yells ]
[ coughing ]
Bill .
- Miss me ? - [ gasps ]
I know what you are .
That 's why I 'm not afraid .
[ groaning ]
[ laughing ]
Well , I know what you are .
A madman .
[ Mike yelping ]
[ grunts ]
Hey , fuckface !
[ groans ]
You wanna play Truth or Dare ?
Here 's a truth .
You 're a sloppy bitch !
Yeah , that 's right !
Let 's dance ! Yippee-ki-yay ...
[ gasps ]
This kills monsters .
If you believe it does .
Beep-beep , motherfucker !
[ howls ]
[ grunts ]
[ choking ]
Holy shit !
[ wheezing ]
Rich !
Oh , Rich !
Hey , Rich , wake up !
Hey .
Yeah , yeah ! There he is , buddy !
Hey , Richie , listen !
I think I got him , man !
I think I killed It !
I did ! I think I killed It for real !
- [ groans ] - [ yelps ]
[ screaming ]
[ gasping ]
Eddie .
Richie .
[ screaming ]
[ gasps ]
[ Pennywise laughing ]
No !
Eddie .
Uh-oh !
[ screaming ]
No !
[ yelping ]
[ gasps ]
[ groaning ]
[ all ] Eddie !
[ Ben ] Eds !
- Eds ! Eds ! - [ Richie ] Eddie !
[ Bill ] Eds , come on , man .
[ Eddie groaning ]
[ Ben ] Be careful ! Be careful !
[ labored breathing ]
Come out and play , Losers !
He 's hurt . He 's hurt really bad .
We gotta get him out of here .
How are we supposed to do that , Richie ?
I almost killed It .
The leper .
My hands around his throat .
And I could feel him choking .
I made him small .
He seemed so weak .
The Shokopiwah .
All living things must abide by
the laws of the shape they inhabit .
[ Ben ] Guys !
There 's a passageway . Through here .
The tunnel .
Pennywise has to make himself small
to get through the entrance of the cavern , right ?
Okay , so , if we can get back there , we can
- force him down to size . - Yeah .
We make him small . Small enough so we can kill him .
I can smell the stink of your fear !
[ Pennywise laughing ]
- Let 's go ! Go ! - [ Ben ] Come on ! Come on !
It 's tight . It 's tight . Be careful !
I need a little rest . Oh , thanks . [ groaning ]
Hey .
Hey , Richie ?
I gotta tell you something .
What ? What 's up , buddy ?
I fucked your mother .
[ laughing ]
[ Pennywise ] Losers out ! [ laughing ]
[ Bill ] Go . Go !
[ yelping ]
[ all screaming ]
[ Pennywise whoops ]
Gotcha !
Whoa !
You filthy little children .
[ laughs ]
You got a plan B , man ? What the hell do we do now ?
You die . That 's what you do .
[ Ben ] Mike ?
There 's more than one way to make someone small .
Oh !
Make him believe that he is .
- [ stutters ] What ? - Make him believe that he is .
Oh ? Me ? Small ? [ laughs ]
I am the Eater of Worlds .
Not to us , you 're not .
You 're just a clown .
[ growling ]
You 're a weak old woman .
The Eater of Worlds .
A headless boy !
Impostor !
[ snarling ]
You 're a mimic !
A mimic !
You 're a fucking bully !
You 're just a fucking clown !
Eater of Worlds !
A clown ! A dumb fucking clown !
[ Bill ] Clown !
A leper !
[ Beverly ] You 're a clown !
You 're a clown !
A painting !
[ Ben ] You 're a clown !
[ Bill ] I 'm not afraid of you anymore !
A motherfucking stupid mummy !
[ Mike ] You 're a clown !
Clown ! Clown !
- [ all shouting ] - [ Pennywise groaning ]
- [ Mike ] Clown ! - Clown !
You 're a fucking clown !
[ Beverly ] You 're a clown !
- [ Ben ] A stupid mummy ! - Clown !
[ Ben ] Clown , motherfucker !
I am the Eater of Worlds !
[ Ben ] Clown !
- Clown ! - You 're just a clown ! Clown !
- I am the Eater of Worlds ! - [ Ben and Bill ] A clown !
- [ Pennywise snarls ] - [ Bill ] Whoa !
[ losers chanting ] A clown ! A clown !
[ screaming ]
[ Mike ] No one 's afraid of you .
No one 's scared of you .
[ losers ] Clown ! Clown !
Clown . Clown . Clown .
[ moaning ]
- Clown . - Clown .
A clown .
With a scared , beating heart .
[ whimpering ]
[ heart beating ]
- [ snarls ] - [ yelps ]
- [ whining ] - [ heart continues beating ]
[ screaming ]
Look at you .
You 're all grown up .
[ laughing ]
[ wheezing ]
[ dying breath ]
Eddie . Eddie .
Eddie . We got Pennywise , man .
Eddie ?
- [ crying ] - [ rumbling ]
[ Beverly ] Richie .
He 's gone .
He 's all right . No , he 's just hurt .
We gotta get him outta here . He 's hurt . Ben .
Bill , he 's okay . We gotta get him outta here .
Bev .
Richie . [ sniffles ]
What ?
Honey , he 's dead .
We have to go . Come on . Come on , Richie .
We gotta go .
- Come on , buddy . Come on . - [ rumbling intensifies ]
[ Ben ] Let him go , man . Let him go .
- [ Bill ] Got it . - [ all urging ]
We can still help him , guys ! We can still help him !
[ Ben ] Go ! Go ! Get up !
Guys , we can still help him !
[ Richie ] No ! Eddie !
Eddie !
[ Mike ] Come on ! Let 's go !
Come on ! Let 's go !
Move , move !
- Move , move ! - [ Beverly ] Run !
[ Mike ] Run !
[ all yelping ]
- Eddie ! - No , no , no !
Eddie !
We gotta get in there and get him !
He 's still in there !
Eddie !
[ Ben ] You know what ?
Eddie would have hated this , guys .
What ? Cleaning ourselves in dirty water ?
Yeah .
He 'd be telling us we 'd get streptococcal something .
- [ chuckles ] - Yeah .
But he would have made us laugh , though .
Oh , yeah .
He 'd be looking out for us .
The way he always was .
Ain 't that right , Richie ?
[ sobbing ]
Hey .
Oh .
Thank you .
I don 't have my glasses on ,
so I don 't know who you people are , but thank you .
[ all laughing ]
I legit can 't find my glasses .
You 're serious ?
- Glasses ? - Go that way .
Around here somewhere ?
- I can 't see them . - Oh , I see them . Right there .
- Where ? - Look . Right ...
If you just go , like ...
Anybody have any luck ?
Hey , guys .
Look .
Nothing lasts forever .
I can 't go home like this , guys .
My mom will kill me .
Dude , you 've been gone for 24 straight hours .
Your face is definitely on a milk carton by now .
Also , that puke smells worse than your mom 's slippers .
[ Young Beverly ] Oh , shut up , Richie .
Okay , first of all , my mom 's slippers
smell like potpourri , asshole .
No , they don 't .
Yes , they do . And , also , how would you know
what they smell like in the first place ?
[ Young Mike ] Can we just keep it quiet ,
please , until we get home ?
[ Young Ben ] " Potpourri " is literally a French word
meaning " rotten pot . "
[ Young Richie ] I knew there was something rotten about it .
- [ cell phone ringing ] - [ Bill sighs ]
- Mike ? - Hey . [ chuckles ]
I just thought I 'd check up on you .
You know , just to see if you learned
how to finish a book for once .
[ chuckling ]
I just finished the first chapter .
And I think I actually know where I 'm going this time .
Good .
Say , can I ask you a question ?
Sure .
Why do you think we 're not forgetting ?
You know , like last time ?
Maybe ' cause It 's dead .
Or maybe ' cause we have more
we want to remember than we want to forget .
I like that one .
You decide what you want to do ?
About leaving Derry ?
Man , I 've been in this cell for 27 years .
Just seeing what It wanted me to .
I think it 's time I saw the sky for a change .
Go get it , Mikey .
Oh , did you get the letter ?
[ stammers ]
What letter ?
You 'll know when you see it .
Well , hold on . I just got the mail .
We all got one .
[ Bill ] Patricia Uris ?
Just ...
Just read it .
Okay .
And call me . Anytime .
I will .
And , Bill ,
I love you , man .
I love you , too .
All right . See you around .
[ Stanley ] Dear Losers ,
I know what this must seem like ,
but this isn 't a suicide note .
You 're probably wondering why I did what I did .
It 's because I knew I was too scared to go back .
And if we weren 't together ,
if all of us alive weren 't united ,
I knew we 'd all die .
So , I made the only logical move .
I took myself off the board .
Did it work ?
[ Stanley sighs ]
Well , if you 're reading this , you know the answer .
I lived my whole life afraid .
Afraid of what would come next .
Afraid of what I might leave behind .
Don 't .
Be who you want to be .
Be proud .
You sleep okay ?
Yeah .
I had a beautiful dream .
[ Stanley ] And if you find someone worth holding on to ,
never ever let them go .
Follow your own path .
Wherever that takes you .
Think of this letter as a promise .
[ Eddie ] A promise I 'm asking you to make .
[ Mike ] To me .
[ Ben ] To each other .
[ Beverly ] An oath .
[ Stanley ] See , the thing about being a Loser
is you don 't have anything to lose .
So ...
[ Young Richie ] Be true .
[ Young Eddie ] Be brave .
[ Young Mike ] Stand .
[ Young Beverly ] Believe .
[ Young Bill ] And don 't ever forget ...
[ Young Stanley ] We 're Losers ,
and we always will be .
Subtitles by explosiveskull Sync by GoldenBeard